[Music]
sunlife is adding even more flexibility
to our dental plans with roax dental
members can roll over a portion of their
unused annual maximum for use in the
future members just need to have at
least one paid claim and can't go over
their annual spend threshold here's how
that
works Joe has an annual maximum of
$1,500 he went to the dentist twice and
had paid claims of $600 which is below
his annual spend threshold of
$700 at the end of the year he will add
$500 to his roax
account members can add to their rmax
accounts each year up to the account
maximum the additional maximum dollars
can be spent on any preventive basic or
major covered service and don't worry if
you have a maximum rollover account with
your current plan those dollars won't be
lost we can easily transfer current
account values over to the new plan
ready to see how the benefits can add up
use our new rmax calculators at
sunlife.com dental tools to create your
own custom example and see how the
benefits add up